Leagues
Cup champions in two thousand and twenty three
Moss is an old calendar second
Save in the first four minutes
This one better than the first
And ana coming through come ana first time undy
Cutting it back
Rotunda curling it off the post
And the rebound is over
He's complimentary
He's gonna pay me
Oh
Wide again
How about that for a ball
Yeah
Big switch over to robert
Taylor
Robert taylor want to go
Miami made one now
Set piece now for cruiser calendar to the pitch for the first time
For
Thought about it
Niall in calendar could get to it and tuna stores
Oreo and tuna levels
The match for cru messi trying to get behind
Messi is in
The flag is down
Messi oh
Cutting it back to joseph
Who taps it in
And now the flag does come up
The delayed offside flag
Put it in
And the other way
Magnificent
And everything's about opening the game
Going for a great ball from i think he's outside
Messy with kazan off his line
Messy
Are not allowed to find the space to pick up
As you'd expect
Almada serves in over a ram calendar
Was not taking any chances
He sends it out making into al alda mei
One of all to martinez joseph
Martinez is just over
Is messi driving forward over to robert taylor
Taylor cutting it back
Martinez
Oh my word
He has done it again
Little messy
Three goals in less than an hour of play for miami play by bats
Robert taylor
Oh
What a gold
Sun sessional from the robert taylor and miami flying three now before half time
Ronald hernandez allot coming back to help defend taylor to his left
Robert taylor up and running robert taylor the post
And then oh
Does he love playing with lionel messi
Robert taylor second to his left
Slides into martinez
To taylor ausand a wonderful
Save to deny robert taylor barry
What a cutback still miko berry and right a drake calendar
In the end he got down quick
Calendar pairing it away
He was positioned well
And he made the same
He's now watching me play with messi
Oh
That's a penalty at n went down
It is given
So atlanta will have a chance to pull one back very late from the penalty spot
And is this going to be a straight red
It will be almana is saved by
No stopping for a good low in the touch from calendar and then in aloo
Mass contributing in the book
Let's say pushes it over the bar
This is so good promising attacking was the first to talk to mai
Just why mai
He turns into space through from martinez who goes down and again
This instead of messi joseph
Martinez scores
I went the wrong way
Messi gives up the penalty to his still robert
Taylor floats towards joseph
Martinez
Samaa
It continues to go perfect
Drives it in and it's put in at the back post
Enrique is in front of it
But he's gonna have a second look because ball
But he is offside
The goal is taken away
Messi miami magic continues
Giovanni chase it all
I want to say
But puts it in
And the flag comes over to land on the
His sixth goal for robert taylor is in
Robert taylor saved by pa in the rebound
Is that messi passed for five good ball and
The answer from the thirty year old argentine kongo
Come on
Go
The dream continues for bernard kongo
For fun
Florida and
Dallas as the third
And so this is our house
By the supporters here in dallas who paid hundreds of dollars to come here
Alba coming back
Minutes after coming on
The eighteen year old from miami gets one back three to two
Also lasco keeping it himself a cutting it back
Oh
What an intervention
But robert taylor at an angle
Well messi tried
He's gonna clip it in
Oh my
Does anyone this ball whipped in
To make it two two over the bar
He misses over and miami is through
He does the eighteen year old winning the shootout
Little messes miami story continues under the quarterfinals of league cup still kermai
He has time
He's gonna slide into joseph martinez
Messi broken up by awful
Like there was a handball from the charlotte defender
Absolutely miami ahead
Awful steps up and as well to win it
Awful from distance speed ski from distance strikes here
This is aa making a save
But a robert taylor taylor coming back to
Serves it in on
Is there he missed it is with messi on the ball over the gomez cutting it
He intervene campana still on it
Though as it came out for wanda
Oh
Nobody coming to campana and stores another one
This decade
The most points
The most goals scored
The fewest goals conceded since two thousand and twenty
Here's a chance on martz and a goal
Joseph martinez three minutes in opens
The scoring for miami
May be a better option defending first
They're reacting
That brought here from walker tina has time to turn into messy advantage play
Messy driving forward messi from du
What can he not do
We are watching greatness and anyone
They play two fords to high press
The two center backs turn them over
Taylor's gonna keep coming forward
Jordi alba wants him behind
Toro might be in a chance for a
Through for donovan about calendar goal is open
All disguising by wagner another chance to cross
He sends it
Try on spectacular
And then gustag sends it over with the offside flag up anyway
But i've really fokner floating it in
Flicking it off
Plus dismisses
Flicked on off of calendar
Great yet land yet lin through taruisa play off
It's their number
The magic number
It's a miami dream
It's a philadelphia nightmare
The leagues cup final is underway into miami and nashville sc
All miller was forward
Drew alma into robert taylor
Robert taylor panico makes the same gramaski in the middle taylor
Cutting it to his right
Trying to get it to for asking
And inevitable love it
Love it to the back post will rising on jordi alba
Cutting it back martinez
It was
Just under three hundred less than miami messi again the
To his right samson calendar makes the same and the time
Motor the step over move to who sketch settles
Campana wants it behind who sketch for apana
We're gonna on in to win lacup over
To begin the show that second go waits for panic
Go to commit gives miami
Saved by calendar miami advantage after two rounds needed to make a decision
He gets paid to go to go
Chris off against
To keep that alive
Donald from drake calmust score for nashville in round eleven
Finishes the script
The first ever league cup champions are a little mess
Wait for champion
Leagues
Cup champions in two thousand and twenty three
The first ever winners